WASEEM KASHIF

Frontend Developer | Mentor | Team Leader

https://profile-portfolio-nine.vercel.app/ +974-3007-8398 @ waseemqulandar@gmail.com



STRENGTHS



Coding Expert

Proficient in Next.js, Tailwind, JavaScript



Problem Solver

Innovative approach to challenges



Team Player

Excellent collaboration skills

SKILLS

HTML **CSS** JavaScript Rest API's Next.js TypeScript GIT React.js Vue.js SvelteKit Redux Tailwind CSS Material UI

Magento

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Igra University

Pre-Engineering HSSC II

Aga Khan Heigher Secondary School.

- **=** 2014 2016
- ♥ Karimabad FB Area, Karachi, PK

Matric (science)

The Aga Khan School

= 2011 - 2014

♥ Kharadar, Karachi, PK

SUMMARY

Passionate Frontend Developer with a knack for creating intuitive and high-performing web applications.

I excel at motivating, mentoring & developing teams of less experienced developers. I have 5+ years of experience and ambitious web design professional seeking an opportunity as a front-end developer. Detail-oriented professional with an associate degree in computer science and proven experience with a web development firm and Ecommerce Group.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Developer

Ansar Gallery, A&H MARKET

Senior front-end web developer for ahmarket.com.

- I was hired to develop the ahmarket website, a leading e-commerce platform in the
- This website is currently on the Magento CMS platform and providin services in GCC countries.

Frontend Developer

Uconnect Technologies

m 02/2021 - 02/2024 ♀ Gilgit, PK

Worked on various web development projects

- Contributed to the development of 10+ websites
- Responsible for converting figma designs into real time responsive web applications using required technologies.

Junior Frontend Developer

Uconnect Technologies

= 2020 - 2021

♀ Gilgit, PK

Assisted in the development of web applications

- Worked on multiple small web development projects
- Improved web skills by learings and working on real time projects.
- Received 'Rising Star' award for outstanding performance.

INDUSTRY EXPERTISE

Front-end develoment Backend, DevOps

LANGUAGES

English + Urdu **Proficient**